Henry A. Kissinger Papers, Part III: Guide to the Yale University Library Collection
Manuscripts and Archives
- Restricted Files, 1947 - 2006; Series III
  - Memoranda of conversation
    - Alwi Shihab, Sep 5, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 60)
    - Kartika Soekarno, Sep 5, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 61)
    - Abdurrahman Wahid, Sep 7, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 62)
    - Hugo Banzer Suárez, Sep 8, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 63)
    - Zeng Peiyan, Sep 22, 2000 (Box 170, Folder 64)
    - Jiang Zemin, China, Mar 20, 2001 (Box 170, Folder 65)
    - Yang Jiechi on United States arms sale to Taiwan of eight submarines, Apr 19, 2001 (Box 170, Folder 66)
    - Xanana Gusmao, May 18, 2001 (Box 170, Folder 67)
    - Igor Ivanov on ABM treaty, NATO, and Ariel Sharon's visit to Russia, Sep 24, 2001 (Box 170, Folder 68)
    - Gamal Mubarak, New York, Jan 29, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 69)
    - Hani Al Hassan, New York, Apr 29, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 70)
    - Jorge G. Castaneda, May 9, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 71)
    - Tang Jiaxuan, Sep 13, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 72)
    - Victor Medvedchuk on Ukraine-United States relations, Nov 18, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 73)
    - Wu Bangguo and Zhu Rongji, Dec 2-4, 2002 (Box 170, Folder 74)
    - Yang Jiechi, New York, Feb 4, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 1)
    - Yang Jiechi on North Korea and Iraq, Mar 28, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 2)
    - Roh Moo Hyun, New York, May 12, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 3)
    - Karsten Voight, Nov 6, 2003, Circa 2003 (Box 171, Folder 4)
    - Daniel Doctoroff and Jay Kriegel, Nov 7, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 5)
    - China meetings, Nov 9-14, 2003 (Box 171, Folder 6)
    - Tang Jiaxuan, China, Jan 13, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 7)
    - Wen Jiabao, China, Jan 13, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 8)
    - Japanese Diet delegation to the United States, Jan 14, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 9)
    - Vladimir Putin, Russia, Mar 2, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 10)
    - Dai Bingguo, Mar 4, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 11)
    - Yang Jiechi and Tang Guocai, Apr 7, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 12)
    - Frank Lutz, Apr 26, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 13)
    - Peter Blackmore, Apr 30, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 14)
    - Democratic Party of Japan delegation, Apr 30, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 15)
    - Yang Jiechi, May 25, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 16)
    - Carol Basir, New York, Jun 24, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 17)
    - Mikhail Margelov, Sep 22, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 18)
    - Anatoly Zlenko and Valery Kuchynskyi, Oct 19, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 19)
    - Dai Bingguo, Oct 29, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 20)
    - Wolfgang Ischinger, Dec 10, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 21)
    - Yang Jiechi, Dec 21, 2004 (Box 171, Folder 22)
    - Sergei Ivanov, Jan 13, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 23)
    - Vladimir Putin, Moscow, Feb 12, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 24)
    - Zhou Xiaochuan, May 11, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 25)
    - Dai Bingguo, Beijing, May 16, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 26)
    - Li Ruogu, Beijing, May 16, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 27)
    - Hu Jintao, Beijing, May 17, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 28)
    - Dong-young Chung, New York, Jun 29, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 29)
    - Yevgeny Primakov, Moscow, Oct 11, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 30)
    - Vladimir Putin, Moscow, Oct 12, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 31)
    - Sergei Ivanov, Oct 13, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 32)
    - Lu Qiutian, New York, Nov 19, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 33)
    - Dai Bingguo, Dec 6, 2005 (Box 171, Folder 34)
    - Ri Gun, Mar 8, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 35)
    - Walid Jumblatt, Mar 8, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 36)
    - Shaukat Aziz, New York, Apr 5, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 37)
    - Vladimir Putin, Russia, Jun 6, 2006 (Box 171, Folder 38)
  - Trips
    The trips files supplement the memoranda of conversation files, usually providing itineraries, thank you notes, and copies of the memoranda of conversation available in the memoranda of conversation files. However, the trip files contain additional memoranda of conversation not available in the memoranda of conversation files, especially for Kissinger’s trips from 1993 to 1999 when he traveled frequently to China. Major topics covered by memoranda of conversation from these trip files include economic relations, Taiwan, Tibet, and North Korea.
    - China, Nov 7-10, 1989 (Box 171, Folder 39)
    - China, Sep 7-9, 1990 (Box 171, Folder 40)
    - Hungary, Jul 1-2, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 41)
    - China, Sep 6-11, 1991 (Box 171, Folder 42)
    - Kiev and Moscow, Jan 10-15, 1992 (Box 172, Folder 1)
    - Indonesia, Oct 4-6, 1992 (Box 172, Folder 2)
    - Uzbekistan, Oct 7-8, 1992 (Box 172, Folder 3)
    - St. Petersburg, Oct 8-10, 1992 (Box 172, Folder 4)
    - Moscow, Oct 10-12, 1992 (Box 172, Folder 5)
    - China, Dec 10-12, 1992 (Box 172, Folder 6)
    - Tokyo and China, May 12-19, 1993 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - China and Hong Kong, May 10-16, 1994 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - China, Jan 15-17, 1995 (Box 172, Folder 9)
    - China, Jun 30-Jul 5, 1995 (Box 172, Folder 10)
    - China, Apr 17-21, 1996 (Box 172, Folder 11)
    - China, Sep 3-7, 1996 (Box 172, Folder 12)
    - China, Dec 4-8, 1996 (Box 172, Folder 13)
    - China and Hong Kong, Jun 15-21, 1997 (Box 172, Folder 14)
    - China and Hong Kong, Jun 4-9, 1998 (Box 173, Folder 1)
    - China and South Korea, Sep 1-6, 1998 (Box 173, Folder 2)
    - India, China, and Japan, Jun 7-17, 1999 (Box 173, Folder 3)
- Telephone Conversation Transcript Copies, 1969 - 1974; Series IV
  The files contain photocopies of the declassified and redacted copies of Kissinger’s telephone conversation transcripts (telcons) open to researchers at the Nixon Presidential Library. The telephone conversation transcripts are an extraordinary source on Kissinger’s service as national security advisor and secretary of state, one of the best that exists. The transcripts concern virtually every aspect of Kissinger’s diplomacy and government service as well as his relations with the media, friends, family, and a wider public.
  The original transcripts, archived at the Library of Congress, number more than 15,000 and recount Kissinger’s telephone conversations while in office from 1969 to 1977 nearly verbatim. Kissinger had either a secretary listen to conversations on a “dead key” extension of the phone line and take shorthand notes or had the conversations taped, from which secretaries would later prepare the transcripts.
  The copies in this collection cover only the Nixon presidency from January 1969 to August 1974 and do not include the transcripts from the Ford administration. These files are also missing a small proportion of the transcripts from 1969 to 1974, including all transcripts from April 29, 1972 to May 10, 1972 and individual transcripts from a number of other days. The copies were retained in Part III in order to increase the ease of access to these invaluable historical records.
  Series IV is arranged chronologically.
  The papers are open for research.
  - Transcripts, 1969 January 21-25 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1969 January 27-31 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1969 February 1-6 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1969 February 7-17 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1969 February 18-22 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1969 March 3-7 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1969 March 8-13 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1969 March 14-18 (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1969 March 19-28 (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1969 March 29-31 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1969 April 1-4 (Box 174, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1969 April 5-14 (Box 174, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1969 April 15-17 (Box 174, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1969 April 18-24 (Box 174, Folder 14)
  - Transcripts, 1969 April 25-30 (Box 174, Folder 15)
  - Transcripts, 1969 May 1-13 (Box 174, Folder 16)
  - Transcripts, 1969 May 14-27 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1969 May 28-30 (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1969 June 2-11 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1969 June 12-18 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1969 June 19-25 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1969 June 26-30 (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1969 July 1-10 (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1969 July 11-16 (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1969 July 17-22 (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1969 August 5-26 (Box 175, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1969 September 1-11 (Box 175, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1969 September 12-23 (Box 175, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1969 September 24-30 (Box 175, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1969 October 1-9 (Box 175, Folder 14)
  - Transcripts, 1969 October 10-20 (Box 175, Folder 15)
  - Transcripts, 1969 November 1-6 (Box 175, Folder 16)
  - Transcripts, 1969 November 10-15 (Box 175, Folder 17)
  - Transcripts, 1969 November 17-22 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1969 November 24-28 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1969 December 1-5 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1969 December 8-12 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1969 December 13-18 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1969 December 19-26 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1969 December 29-31 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1970 January 3-10 (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1970 January 12-15 (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1970 January 16-19 (Box 176, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1970 January 20-23 (Box 176, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1970 January 24-29 (Box 176, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1970 January 30-31 (Box 176, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1970 February 1-18 (Box 176, Folder 14)
  - Transcripts, 1970 February 19-27 (Box 176, Folder 15)
  - Transcripts, 1970 March 2-4 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1970 March 5-11 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1970 March 12-17 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1970 March 19-23 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1970 March 24-27 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1970 April 6-13 (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1970 April 14-16 (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1970 April 17-20 (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1970 April 21-24 (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1970 April 25-30 (Box 177, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1970 May 1-4 (Box 177, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1970 May 5-7 (Box 177, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1970 May 8-11 (Box 177, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1970 May 12-21 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1970 May 22-31 (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1970 June 1-5 (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1970 June 6-12 (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1970 June 13-17 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1970 June 18-24 (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1970 June 25-30 (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1970 July 1-9 (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1970 July 10-14 (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1970 July 15-21 (Box 178, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1970 July 22-31 (Box 178, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1970 August 4-10 (Box 178, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1970 August 11-18 (Box 178, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1970 August 19-31 (Box 178, Folder 14)
  - Transcripts, 1970 September 2-12 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1970 September 14-16 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1970 September 17-19 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1970 September 20-21 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1970 September 22-23 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1970 September 24-25 (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1970 October 5-7 (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1970 October 8-10 (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1970 October 12-15 (Box 179, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1970 October 16-19 (Box 179, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1970 October 21-23 (Box 179, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1970 October 24-31 (Box 179, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1970 November 2-10 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1970 November 13-19 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1970 November 20-21 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1970 November 23-27 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1970 November 28-30 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1970 December 1-5 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1970 December 7-9 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1970 December 10-14 (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1970 December 15-18 (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1970 December 19-22 (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1970 December 23-31 (Box 180, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1971 January 4-11 (Box 180, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1971 January 12-20 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1971 January 21-29 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1971 February 1-7 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1971 February 8-16 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1971 February 17-23 (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1971 February 24-28 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1971 March 1-3 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1971 March 4-11 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1971 March 12-16 (Box 181, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1971 March 17-19 (Box 181, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1971 March 20-21 (Box 181, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1971 March 22 (Box 181, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1971 March 23-25 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1971 March 26-27 (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1971 March 28-31 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1971 April 1-5 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1971 April 6-8 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1971 April 9-14 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1971 April 15-19 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1971 April 20-28 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1971 May 10-12 (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1971 May 13-15 (Box 182, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1971 May 17-19 (Box 182, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1971 May 20-24 (Box 182, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1971 May 25-29 (Box 182, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1971 June 1-5 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1971 June 7-11 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1971 June 12-17 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1971 June 18-21 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1971 June 22-28 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1971 June 29-30 (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1971 July 1-17 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1971 July 18-23 (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1971 July 24-28 (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1971 July 29-30 (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1971 August 2-4 (Box 183, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1971 August 5-10 (Box 183, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1971 August 11-14 (Box 183, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1971 August 16-20 (Box 183, Folder 14)
  - Transcripts, 1971 August 21-27 (Box 183, Folder 15)
  - Transcripts, 1971 August 28-31 (Box 183, Folder 16)
  - Transcripts, 1971 September 1-7 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1971 September 8-15 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1971 September 16-30 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1971 October 1-5 (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1971 October 6-11 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1971 October 12-15 (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1971 October 16-30 (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1971 November 1-9 (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1971 November 10-16 (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1971 November 17-23 (Box 184, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1971 November 24-30 (Box 184, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1971 December 1-3 (Box 184, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1971 December 4-6 (Box 184, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1971 December 7-10 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1971 December 11-14 (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1971 December 15-16 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1971 December 17-23 (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1972 January 3-12 (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1972 January 14-18 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1972 January 19-25 (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1972 January 26-31 (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1972 February 1-8 (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1972 February 9-14 (Box 185, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1972 February 15-29 (Box 185, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1972 March 3-10 (Box 185, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1972 March 11-18 (Box 185, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1972 March 27-31 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1972 April 3-5 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1972 April 7-9 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1972 April 10-14 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1972 April 15-16 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1972 April 17-26 (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1972 April 28 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1972 May 11-12 (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1972 May 13-14 (Box 186, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1972 May 15-17 (Box 186, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1972 May 18-19 (Box 186, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1972 June 2-4 (Box 186, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1972 June 6-8 (Box 186, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1972 June 10-15 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1972 June 21-26 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1972 June 27-29 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1972 June 30 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1972 July 3-6 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1972 July 7-10 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1972 July 11-17 (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1972 July 20-22 (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1972 July 24-26 (Box 187, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1972 July 27-29 (Box 187, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1972 August 2-3 (Box 187, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1972 August 4-7 (Box 187, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1972 August 8-11 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1972 August 12-21 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1972 August 22-30 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1972 September 2-7 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1972 September 8-18 (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1972 September 19-20 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1972 September 21-22 (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1972 September 23-28 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1972 September 29-30 (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1972 October 2-5 (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1972 October 6-7 (Box 188, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1972 October 12-14 (Box 188, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1972 October 15-23 (Box 188, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1972 October 24-25 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1972 October 26-27 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1972 October 28-31 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1972 November 1-2 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1972 November 3-7 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1972 November 8-14 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1972 November 15-20 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1972 November 26-28 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1972 November 29-30 (Box 189, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1972 December 1-10 (Box 189, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1972 December 12-16 (Box 189, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1972 December 17-18 (Box 189, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1972 December 19-20 (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1972 December 23-26 (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1973 January 2-5 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1973 January 6-16 (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1973 January 17 (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1973 January 18-19 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1973 January 20-24 (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1973 January 25 (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1973 January 26-27 (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1973 January 29-31 (Box 190, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1973 February 1-5 (Box 190, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1973 February 6-20 (Box 190, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1973 February 21 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1973 February 22-24 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1973 February 26-28 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1973 March 1-2 (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1973 March 3-6 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1973 March 7-9 (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1973 March 10-13 (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1973 March 14-15 (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1973 March 16-28 (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1973 March 29-31 (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1973 April 2-5 (Box 191, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1973 April 6-9 (Box 191, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1973 April 10-13 (Box 191, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1973 April 14-17 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1973 April 18-21 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1973 April 22-24 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1973 April 25-26 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1973 April 27-30 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1973 May 1-3 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1973 May 11-14 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1973 May 15-24 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1973 May 25-30 (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1973 June 1-3 (Box 192, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1973 June 4-10 (Box 192, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1973 June 11-14 (Box 192, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1973 June 15-18 (Box 192, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1973 June 19-23 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1973 June 24-26 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1973 June 27-30 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1973 July 2-9 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1973 July 10-11 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1973 July 12-13 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1973 July 14-16 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1973 July 17-19 (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1973 July 20-28 (Box 193, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1973 July 29-31 (Box 193, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1973 August 1-7 (Box 193, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1973 August 8-11 (Box 193, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1973 August 12-15 (Box 193, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1973 August 16-18 (Box 193, Folder 14)
  - Transcripts, 1973 August 20-23 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1973 August 24-31 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1973 September 1-6 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1973 September 7-10 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1973 September 11-15 (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1973 September 16-18 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1973 September 19-21 (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1973 September 22-30 (Box 194, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 1-3 (Box 194, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 6 (Box 194, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 7 (Box 194, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 8-9 (Box 194, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 10-11 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 12-13 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 14-16 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 17-19 (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 23 (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 24 (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 25 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 26 (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 27-29 (Box 195, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1973 October 30-31 (Box 195, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1973 November 1-17 (Box 195, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1973 November 19-28 (Box 195, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1973 November 29-30 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1973 December 3-8 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1973 December 15-31 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1974 January 1-6 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1974 January 7-10 (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1974 January 21-25 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1974 January 26-31 (Box 196, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1974 February 1-7 (Box 196, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1974 February 8-14 (Box 196, Folder 9)
  - Transcripts, 1974 February 15-27 (Box 196, Folder 10)
  - Transcripts, 1974 March 5-12 (Box 196, Folder 11)
  - Transcripts, 1974 March 13-17 (Box 196, Folder 12)
  - Transcripts, 1974 March 18-21 (Box 196, Folder 13)
  - Transcripts, 1974 March 22-30 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - Transcripts, 1974 April 10-17 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - Transcripts, 1974 April 18-24 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - Transcripts, 1974 April 25-27 (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - Transcripts, 1974 May 31 (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - Transcripts, 1974 June 1-6 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - Transcripts, 1974 June 7-21 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - Transcripts, 1974 June 22-26 (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - Transcripts, 1974 July 10-18 (Box 197, Folder 9)